so the thing that i want to show you
所以我想给你看的东西
today is a new Phaneuf new spring
今天是Phaneuf的新春天
features new spring supported features
具有新的弹簧支持功能
in integer 15 you may know about this
在整数15中，您可能知道
the spring initializer which is a wizard
春天的初始化是一个向导
to create a skeleton project based on a
创建一个基于
set of dependencies and it's integrated
一组依赖关系，它是集成的
in indy ie since folded up on I want to
在印，即因为折叠起来我想
show you some new cool stuff that that
给你看一些新奇的东西
has been added in 15 as you may know
如您所知，已添加15
springwood 123 is about to be released
Springwood 123即将发布
and there's plenty of new features and
而且有很多新功能
IntelliJ IDEA shifting already supports
IntelliJ IDEA转换已支持
them must be new metadata support about
它们必须是有关新元数据的支持
new features about configuration keys
有关配置密钥的新功能
intelligent edgy 15 is also much much
智能前卫15也有很多
smarter about the spring model and gives
更聪明的弹簧模型，并给
you a better hint about the dependencies
您可以更好地了解依赖关系
in your project and the candidates that
在您的项目和候选人中
you can use for injection points15 also
您也可以使用注射点15
introduced support for the Yemen format
引入了对也门格式的支持
alongside the properties format and
以及属性格式和
finally you also see that when you
最后，当你
create a new project using the using the
使用创建一个新项目
wizard plenty of stuff will be
向导将有很多东西
configured for you automatically ok so
自动为您配置好吧
let's get started you probably know this
让我们开始吧，您可能知道这一点
website right that allows you to create
网站权利，可让您创建
very easily a new project so you shop
一个新项目很容易，所以您购物
for dependencies and basically to the
对于依赖关系，基本上
spring good version you want to use the
您要使用的春季版
build system that you want to use you
建立您要使用的系统
can see all the options there you can
可以在那里看到所有选项
download that project it's a zip file
下载该项目是一个zip文件
then you can unzip it and you can
然后您可以解压缩它
integrate that in the ID of course these
将这些集成到ID中
are manual steps that you have to that
是您必须执行的手动步骤
you have to do to get started and it
您必须要做的就是开始
would be much better if you could do
如果可以的话会更好
that right from right from your ID
从您的ID右到右
without leaving it so to do so you can
不用离开它就可以这样做
click on this create new project button
单击此创建新项目按钮
and choose initializer so that's not new
然后选择初始化程序，这样就不新鲜了
it's already there in 40 not one I'm
我已经有40个人了
just going
刚去
to keep the default right I'm going to
保持默认权限，我要
take the latest spring good release
采取最新的春季好发布
what's new in 15 is that you can search
15的新功能是您可以搜索
for dependencies and its search not only
依赖关系及其搜索
in the name of the dependency but also
以依赖的名义
in the description you can also collapse
在说明中您也可以折叠
items and even though if you search for
项目，即使您搜索
something that's collapse it will give
崩溃的东西会给
you a hint that there are some items
你暗示有些东西
here I which are a little bit so for the
在这里我有点
purpose of this of this simple
这个简单的目的
application we're not going to build an
应用程序，我们不会构建一个
app I'm going to choose web and actuator
我要选择网络和执行器的应用程序
right so next and let's say let's call
好吧，接下来，让我们打电话
that just what we know in 10 to 15 okay
那就是我们在10到15知道的
so when you do that there is many things
所以当你这样做的时候，有很多事情
that are happening you can see that if
发生的事情，你可以看到，如果
the the project could automatically
该项目可以自动
imported so you can just start coding a
已导入，因此您可以开始编码
default run configuration was also
默认运行配置也是
created so basically you can just run a
创建的基本上就可以运行
new app is basically starting there is
新的应用程序基本上是从那里开始的
also if you go into project structure if
如果你进入项目结构
you look into a physics you can see that
你看着物理学，你会看到
is spring related fur
与春天有关的皮草
okay sorry right so basically everything
好的，对不起，所以基本上一切
is configured for you you can just start
为您配置完毕，您就可以开始
writing actually the business logic um
实际编写业务逻辑
for your application so the first thing
对于您的应用程序来说，第一件事
I want to show you is what you you all
我想告诉你你就是你所有人
know probably actually using spring boot
知道可能实际上是使用Spring Boot
and interrogate you probably own already
询问你可能已经拥有了
the content assistance for configuration
内容协助配置
key so basically you type a few
键，所以基本上你输入一些
keystrokes corresponding to a key that
对应于某个键的击键
you're searching and you get content
您正在搜索并获得内容
assistance you can also default value
协助您也可以预设值
documentation link to links to the code
文档链接到代码链接
so you there's plenty of things that you
所以你有很多事情
let you get out of the box but in in 15
让您开箱即用，但在15分钟内
and in springwood one up three we've had
在斯普林伍德，三分之一
it more more feature to it and the first
它有更多的功能，第一个
thing is deprecated support so i know
东西已弃用，所以我知道
that there is a key called spring dutton
那里有个钥匙叫做Spring Dutton
vasilich prefix which is used to
vasilich前缀，用于
configure year DMC prefix for the app
为应用程序配置年份DMC前缀
and in in one not three we actually
在三分之一中，我们实际上
think we actually discovered that the
认为我们实际上发现了
namespace with that key 11 so we will
具有该键11的名称空间，因此我们将
name it to something else so if i search
将其命名为其他名称，以便搜索
for spring MVC prefix you can see the
对于Spring MVC前缀，您可以看到
new one appears at the bottom but the
新的出现在底部，但
other one does not and the reason why is
另一个没有，原因是
it up eat right the reason why is
吃起来正确的原因是
because it will it will be at the bottom
因为它将在底部
it will always be at the bottom and it
它将始终位于底部，并且
will be marked as being deprecated so i
将被标记为已弃用，所以我
invoke the documentation i can see that
调用文档，我可以看到
the key has been deprecated and I can
密钥已被弃用，我可以
also see what the new case but there is
还可以看到有什么新情况
also an intention so art enter as you
也是一种意图，所以艺术会随着你而进入
all know then it will offer me to switch
所有人都知道，那么它将为我提供切换
to the new key basically and it will fix
到新的密钥，它将修复
the configuration for me the other thing
配置对我来说另一件事
that we added in 123 in spring good one
我们在春季的123中添加的好一个
two three is more more assistance for
二三是更多的帮助
value discovery so if i take the
价值发现，所以如果我接受
hibernate the yellow to load I can see
休眠黄色即可看到
that now I get this really nice
现在我变得非常好
completion with value and documentation
具有价值和文件的完成
if I invoke the documentation here I can
如果我在这里调用文档，我可以
also see the list of possible values you
另请参阅可能的值列表
can see that the type e string so there
可以看到类型为e的字符串
is nothing where we could actually fetch
什么都不是我们可以实际获取的
those values and these are the these
这些值，这些是这些
values are actually stored in the
值实际上存储在
metadata so in additional additional
元数据，所以在其他方面
entries in the metadata and you'll see
元数据中的条目，您将看到
that in a minute in IntelliJ IDEA 15 we
一分钟后，我们在IntelliJ IDEA 15中
also automatically detect that anonym is
还会自动检测到匿名
the target ad for property and we we
财产的目标广告，我们
basically extract the values for you so
基本上为您提取值，因此
if you look you basically get the same
如果你看你基本上得到相同的
thing except this is actually this is
除了这件事，这实际上是
actually read from the code itself so
实际上是从代码本身读取的
IntelliJ is inspecting your code
IntelliJ正在检查您的代码
figuring out the reason I am so going on
弄清楚我这样做的原因
the value fetching the the documentation
获取文档的价值
and you get you get that automatically
你会自动得到
out of the box and also the same nice
开箱即用，也一样不错
list of values there is also a better
值列表也有一个更好的
support for third-party a configuration
支持第三方配置
key so if i take flyaway for instance
关键，所以如果我以飞走为例
fly away by basically non migrated to
基本上没有迁移到
say something and I try to go to it I
说些什么，然后我尝试去做
don't have soil in my class pass at the
我班上的土壤没有通过
moment so basically there is nothing and
现在基本上没有任何东西
there is no real information in the
没有真实的信息
metadata about the documentation but if
有关文档的元数据，但如果
I adfly way to my project and I go back
我向我的项目宣传，然后回去
making sure it's imported first making
确保先进口
sure it's important first I guess yes it
首先确定它很重要我想是的
is now then I get also the original
现在是那时，我也得到了原始的
documentation on the under setter itself
设定者本身的文档
which will allow me to basically
这将使我基本上
understand what what that property does
了解该物业的功能
even though there is no full description
即使没有完整的说明
in the metadata right so there is also
在元数据中，所以也有
bunch of stuff that fault in that one
一堆东​​西在那一个故障
did on its own and so in intelligent
靠自己做，所以很聪明
reaction to certain types and what will
对某些类型的反应以及会发生什么
yet we'll use that experience to bundle
但是我们将利用这种经验来捆绑
that in the metadata format so that
以元数据格式
everybody can use it in a consistent way
每个人都可以以一致的方式使用它
first thing is class types you can see
首先是您可以看到的类类型
that this new property is of type class
该新属性的类型为class
and it extends data source so basically
它基本上扩展了数据源
if you do that you get the list of
如果这样做，您将获得
matching classes so the list of matching
匹配的类，因此匹配的列表
a class in your project that that are
您项目中的一个类
like an extension of data source there
像那里的数据源扩展
is only one which is the the 1i i just
只是一个我刚刚的1i
added with Flyway but I can also quickly
加入了Flyway，但我也可以很快
add the GPS tartar which will bring
添加GPS牙垢，它将带来
having it in gps support if I do that
如果我这样做的话，在gps支持中
then spent your things there and only
然后把你的东西花在那里
concrete classes are shown and not
显示具体类而不显示
interface which is good because if you
界面很好，因为如果您
have a lot of interface matching this
有很多与此匹配的界面
may may pollute the list the other type
可能污染列表的另一种类型
that we detect automatically in inter
我们在内部自动检测
jaggi 15 is resource so for instance
jaggi 15是资源，例如
back burner location is a is a which
后燃烧器位置是一个
also from the spring resource
也来自春季资源
abstraction so I'm going to I'm going
抽象，所以我要去
maybe to remove that because i don't
也许要删除它，因为我不
have a I don't have any I don't need to
有我不需要的任何东西
do that to run the app so you all know
这样做可以运行该应用程序，所以大家都知道
about this wonderful spring banner right
关于这个美好的春天横幅吧
so I'm going to customize it so i'm
所以我要自定义它，所以我
going to create a new file call it my
要创建一个新文件，将其命名为my
banner 60 i have a template for it I
横幅60我有一个模板
then i'm going to ask spring good to use
然后我要问春天好用
it and since it's a resource IntelliJ
它，因为它是资源IntelliJ
will basically give you give me a list
基本上会给你我的清单
of things that match and I can basically
匹配的东西，我基本上可以
select it and basically my app is using
选择它，基本上我的应用程序正在使用
the banner now so any the point is
现在横幅，所以任何一点是
property that you define and you expose
您定义并公开的属性
as a resource you'll get automatically
作为资源，您将自动获得
and that can photo completion servicing
这样就可以完成照片的维修
formula type we also support now
我们现在也支持的公式类型
encoding automatically so if your type
自动编码，因此如果您输入
is sorry about that if the type is
如果类型是
called set you automatically get auto
叫集你自动得到自动
completion to that you also get the same
完成，你也得到相同的
thing for mime type so if you look if
笑剧类型的东西，所以如果你看
the tightest mime type you get
你得到的最紧密的哑剧类型
completion for that too and finally we
完成它，最后我们
also have some rules to basically two
也有一些规则，基本上两个
assists to assist you about what kind of
协助您如何
values you can provide such instance if
您可以提供此类实例的值，如果
we take the max file size you can see
我们采用您可以看到的最大文件大小
the documentation that you can indicate
您可以指出的文件
and bok be4 megabyte per kilobyte size
并且每千字节大小博克4兆字节
respectively so if you type something
分别所以如果您输入内容
like that it will it will show you show
这样，它将显示您的节目
you that as a validation error okay so
你这是一个验证错误，所以
these are all good all basically the
这些基本上都是好的
nicest assistance that you get on
您获得的最好的帮助
configuration keys exposed by spring
弹簧暴露的配置键
boot but maybe you don't know that but
启动，但也许你不知道，但是
it's very easy to add your own tree and
添加您自己的树很容易，并且
it's very important to do so because at
这样做非常重要，因为
some point your application will need
有些时候您的应用程序需要
some customization you will need to
您需要进行一些自定义
customize something oh you you may for
定制一些您可能会喜欢的东西
instance work on a rivalry and you want
实例在竞争中工作，您想要
to expose a set of keys to customize the
公开一组键以自定义
way the library works it is very
图书馆的工作方式非常
important at the point that you also
重要的一点是，你也
provide that same nice content
提供相同的漂亮内容
assistance to your user so let's see how
帮助您的用户，让我们看看如何
we can create our own key and configure
我们可以创建自己的密钥并进行配置
springwood to generate the metal it
用斯普林伍德产生金属
automatically for you I'm going to
自动为你，我要
create a class which is hello properties
创建一个您好属性的类
I'm going to create a rello service
我将创建一个rello服务
basically that that that is configured
基本上就是那个配置
with 20 key one is the perfection was
20个关键之一是完美
one is the target right and I'm going to
一个是目标权利，我要
use that innocence just to show you it
用那种纯真向你展示
works hello service I'm going to make
我会做的工作你好服务
this service
这项服务
they're injecting in check Maggie and
他们正在注入支票Maggie和
I'm going to use it puts bus contracts
我要用它放公共汽车合同
to just show a message right something
只是在某件事上显示一条消息
like I'm going to take the prefix a
就像我要带前缀a
space and the target okay very simple
空间和目标还可以，很简单
you can see that intellij us as figure
你可以看到intellij我们的身影
is figuring out that hello properties
正在弄清楚你好属性
it's actually not been it's not a video
其实不是，不是视频
editor in the context which is right
在正确的上下文中编辑
because there is nothing that tells it
因为没有什么可以说明
should be Scannell a beam should be
应该是斯堪内尔光束应该是
created automatically to unable that bad
自动创建到不能那样糟糕
progr to be processed by spring boot
弹簧靴要处理的程序
there is an application in an annotation
注释中有一个应用程序
sorry that you can use which is enabled
抱歉，您可以使用已启用的功能
configuration properties and you can
配置属性，您可以
provide the name of the class you can
提供您可以的课程名称
have as many of those as you want we
有你想要的那么多
will remove them and create the beans
将删除它们并创建bean
for you another alternative is to
对你来说另一种选择是
actually remove that line and put add
实际删除该行，并添加
components on that class and make sure
该类的组件，并确保
that the class is picked up by
该班级由
components canny like LastPass canada of
组件canny之类的LastPass canada
course the best 20 of things that you
当然，你最好的20件事
can do in this case it's it's simple
在这种情况下可以做到的很简单
string but you can have many complex
字符串，但是你可以有很多复杂的东西
types so as as we saw ready you can have
类型，如我们所见，您可以拥有
a class you can have resource you can
一个可以拥有资源的课程
have mime type concept whatever there is
有哑剧类型的概念
going to twin here to make sure that
要在这里双胞胎，以确保
this value is set it isn't for the
设置此值不是为了
moment so let's write to that you can
现在，让我们写信给你
see that you have no assistance
看到你没有帮助
whatsoever well and it's being shown as
一切顺利，并显示为
unknown so if I we start the app I have
未知，所以如果我启动应用程序
my sorry about that probably bigger
我很抱歉那可能更大
would be a good idea at this point you
此时，您将是一个好主意
have the better world message being
有更好的世界信息
printed here okay so how can we fix how
印在这里好吧，我们该如何解决
can we make sure that those metadata are
我们可以确保这些元数据是
created automatically well the GID gives
自动创建好GID给定的
you a nice insane a the annotation
您一个不错的疯子
processor is not on the cross paths so
处理器不在交叉路径上，因此
you can open the documentation we the
您可以打开我们的文档
documentation and you'll figure that out
文档，您会发现
that you have to add this
你必须添加这个
so let's do that and once we've done
所以让我们这样做，一旦完成
that let's rebuild and if we rebuild
让我们重建，如果我们重建
that fight will be generated
将会产生战斗
automatically for you so let's see how
自动为您服务，让我们看看如何
it it's not it's not an unknown key now
不是，现在不是未知密钥
and have my prefix with the
并加上我的前缀
documentation like you would do for any
像您所做的任何文档
spring boot key that you've seen so far
到目前为止您已经看到的spring boot key
can also jump to the code etc so it's
也可以跳到代码等
very very easy to create your own key
创建自己的密钥非常非常容易
and it's very easy to integrate content
而且整合内容非常容易
assistance right in the ID for your own
您自己的ID中的帮助权
keys okay so what else can you do where
键好，那么你还能在哪里做什么
else can you do with the windows
否则你可以用窗户吗
configuration keys and I showed you
配置键，我告诉你
about the deprecated supports I want to
关于我想弃用的支持
quickly quickly demo how you can
快速快速演示如何
actually use that let's say that target
实际使用那个目标
was not the right name for it so a lot
这个名字不是很正确
of targets we don't want that that was
的目标，我们不希望那是
the wrong we want to name it enables
我们要命名的错误启用
dead right so we want to fix that so
完全正确，所以我们要修复此问题
let's add the getter and setter so that
让我们添加getter和setter，以便
we can actually inject the value from
我们实际上可以从
the environment and since we have an API
环境，因为我们有一个API
we don't want to break existing users so
我们不想破坏现有用户，所以
we're going to keep the same methods and
我们将保持相同的方法，
not broke them and just pass to the to
没有打破他们，只是传递给
the new name but you need at some point
新名称，但您有时需要
to tell that this has been deprecated so
告诉我们这个已经过时了
for that there is a annotation you can
为此，您可以注释
use you can give a reason that was a
使用你可以给出一个原因
lousy name and the replacement and the
糟糕的名称和替换以及
replacements able to enemy so if you do
替代品能够敌对，所以如果你这样做
that spring boot will detect the
那个弹簧靴会检测到
annotation will update update your meat
批注将更新更新您的肉
a little too matically IntelliJ IDEA
有点太IntelliJ IDEA
will read that and will tell you but
会读到并告诉你，但是
it's deprecated now and why and of
现在已弃用，为什么和的
course you can also like like you see
当然你也可以喜欢
already like you so ready for the spring
早就喜欢你了
buddakan 50 you can also do that for you
buddakan 50，你也可以为你做
own teeth
自己的牙齿
very quickly there is also support for
很快也有对
application llame so I'm creating a
应用程序llame，所以我要创建一个
yamir file instead I guess I get the
yamir文件而不是我猜我得到了
same experience so let's say server lot
同样的经验，所以说服务器很多
address to say something and if I'm
说些什么的话，如果我是
going here I will get a completion based
去这里，我会根据完成
on the path where I'm located alright so
在我所处的路径上
um I want to show you a bit more stuff
嗯，我想给你看更多的东西
about more other than to use case or you
除了用例或您以外
can basically provide a list of value so
基本上可以提供价值清单，因此
that you get content assistance for the
您将获得内容帮助
value as well but before we do that I
也很有价值，但在我们这样做之前
want to create a custom key so I want to
想创建一个自定义键，所以我想
because of a corner case something that
因为有一个极端的情况
you can't express with properties with
你不能用
the projo but you still all content
Projo，但您仍然满意
assistance you can create the metadata
帮助您创建元数据
when you least you want so there isn't
当你最不想的时候，所以没有
an inspection int that you can so I'd
可以的检查方法，以便
enter again define configuration key for
再次输入定义配置密钥
counter which is located so you
柜台位于
basically write that yourself and
基本上写自己和
basically IntelliJ will assist you you
基本上IntelliJ会为您提供帮助
get full auto completion everywhere if
可以在任何地方获得全自动完成
you if the description is not right you
你如果描述不对你
get some you get some morning you get
得到一些你得到一些早晨你得到
also full of the completion follow
也充满了完成
values etc etc ok so if i go here it's
值等等等，所以如果我去这里
not unknown anymore and i get physically
不再不知道了，我身体上
same content assistance right so let's
同样的内容帮助，所以让我们
let's now give some let's give some
让我们现在给一些让我们给一些
value for the prefix so we want to give
前缀的值，所以我们想给
going to give a list of values for the
给出一个值列表
perfect sphere so to do that I need to
完美的球体，所以我需要做
create additional metadata we're going
创建我们要去的其他元数据
to do that now in a new section
现在在新的部分中进行
something which is new in spring route
春季路线的新事物
when the three which is it again you
当这三个又是你时
will get full of completion for that
为此将充满完成
so that's the alien I want to change I
那就是我要改变的外星人
want to give it a list of values and one
想要给它一个值列表和一个
value is let's say hi in the description
值在说明中打个招呼
which could be I don't know for any time
我可能什么时候都不知道
and you can give it give it another
你可以给它另一个
value which is hello Ledo and form
值是您好Ledo和形式
understand to say something right very
懂得非常正确地说些什么
good intellij idea we'll pick that up
很好的intellij想法，我们会去解决的
and basically will give you a nice
基本上会给你一个很好的
content assistance like you did for like
内容帮助就像您所做的那样
you had fun and I did mistake name
你玩得开心，我弄错了名字
instead of prefix it's not really
而不是前缀不是真的
important but let's just fix that to
重要，但让我们将其修复为
make sure that it's actually meaning
确保它实际上是
island right so we can go back with
对的岛屿，所以我们可以回去
world and let's take it get content
世界，让我们得到满足
assistance for that new one you have
协助您拥有新的
this that's the devil effect I guess
我猜这就是魔鬼的效果
just me interesting anyway right so the
反正就是我很有趣，所以
other thing also you could do is you can
你也可以做的另一件事是你可以
have values provider values provider a
有价值提供者价值提供者a
way to teach the IDE or you can collect
教授IDE的方法，也可以收集
the correct values potential values for
正确的潜在价值
key so one thing which is really really
关键一件事真的是真的
nice is let's take our food let's
很好，是我们吃饭吧
quickly let's quickly create another
快速让我们快速创建另一个
property here so cool let's say it's a
这里的房产很酷，让我们说这是一个
string so if i go here and i create a
字符串，所以如果我去这里，我创建一个
new entry or i can provide a provider
新条目或我可以提供提供商
and in the list of provider there's
在提供商列表中
a few of them so you these are the
其中一些，所以你这些是
options that you have so we spring good
您所拥有的选择，让我们春意盎然
103 may we may add new ones in the
103也许我们可以在
future but one which is interesting is
未来，但有趣的是
spring being reference so spring pin
弹簧是参考，所以弹簧销
reference you're basically teaching the
您基本上在教的参考
ID that the value of the key is the name
密钥的值是名称的ID
of the beam so let's see that I want to
光束，让我们看看我想
for some reason I want to have the
由于某种原因，我想拥有
reference of a spring wind of type
参考类型的弹簧风
integer just to make that easy so I'm
整数只是为了简化操作，所以我
going to give it a target so that it
要给它一个目标，以便它
doesn't return all the beans in the
不返回所有的豆
context but just the ones that I'm
上下文，但仅仅是我
interested in let's create a bunch of
有兴趣让我们创建一堆
material to actually be enough okay if I
材料，如果我真的足够好
do that and that was football right then
做到那就是那时的足球
I get auto completion for beans if i
如果我可以自动完成bean
type a beam that does not exist it will
键入不存在的光束，它将
be shown as an error because the editor
显示为错误，因为编辑器
did not find a bit of such a big lolita
没发现这么大的洛丽塔
right so plenty of stuff that you can do
对，所以你可以做很多事情
remember that the configuration key
记住配置键
assistance is very nice and it has been
协助非常好，而且
improved again and you have new feature
再次改善，您有了新功能
this new feature that are going to be
这项新功能将会
reached in spring good one with 30 pre
在春季达到30的好成绩
next week you can already use them when
下周您已经可以使用它们了
you upgrade 22-250 that's about me
您升级了关于我的22-250
that's that's it for me so maybe again
对我来说就是这样，也许再次
do you know alright thanks Stefan on to
你知道吗，谢谢斯蒂芬
the second part we are going a bit more
第二部分我们要多一点
general leaving the spring boot world
将军离开 spring boot 世界
and moving to spring forward to support
并向前迈进以提供支持
and a brand new thing in IntelliJ 15
和IntelliJ 15中的全新事物
which is the spring model graph so a
这是弹簧模型图，所以
quick recap on the next part
快速回顾下一部分
we are going to look at the new support
我们将看看新的支持
for guillotine annotation on default
用于默认的断头台注释
methods as well as a method parameter
方法以及方法参数
auto auto borrowing we are going to look
自动自动借用我们要看
at the Allies for annotation which is a
在同盟国进行注释，这是一个
very nice way to extend the existing
扩展现有的非常好的方法
annotations in spring and then we are
春天的注释，然后我们
going to look at the application event
要看一下应用程序事件
support which was edit and IntelliJ 15
支持已被编辑和IntelliJ 15
and the second big topic is the spring
第二个大话题是春天
model dependencies graph which is a very
模型依赖图
nice way to understand to visualize and
理解和可视化的好方法
hopefully fix some setup errors with
希望修复一些安装错误
regard to your spring configuration
关于您的弹簧配置
especially for bigger projects and the
特别是对于较大的项目和
last topic I want to talk about today as
我今天想谈的最后一个话题是
our plans for the coming things as we
我们对未来事物的计划
got to spring support in IntelliJ IDEA
在IntelliJ IDEA中获得了弹簧支持
15 dot one okay let's get started with
15点一好，让我们开始吧
spring framework top four so the first
Spring框架排名前四，因此第一
thing i want to show in this class um is
我想在这个班上展示的东西是
the support for the at beam annotation
对at Beam注解的支持
on default methods and interfaces
在默认方法和接口上
default methods have been added in Java
Java中已添加默认方法
8 so a quick recap you can define
8，所以您可以定义一个快速回顾
basically default implementations of an
基本的默认实现
interface in the interface itself so
接口本身在接口本身
basically a little bit like an abstract
基本上有点像摘要
class with a default implementation
具有默认实现的类
which you can override inheritors but
您可以覆盖继承者，但
here on interfaces we have a service of
在界面上，我们提供以下服务
D class or service which is declared in
在中声明的D类或服务
this method or a service and it's
这种方法或服务，
annotated with a pin and so if we
用图钉注释，如果我们
inherit this interface or configuration
继承此接口或配置
will also inherit this beam definition
也将继承此光束定义
let's take a look at the organ
让我们来看看风琴
figuration so we have my configure it
构型，所以我们来配置它
implements all a service config we have
实现我们拥有的所有服务配置
field service of whiskey given type
威士忌给定类型的现场服务
which we are expecting trying to alter
我们期望尝试改变
wire it
连线
and if we go on the edit or gutter icon
如果我们继续编辑或装订线图标
we can navigate to the auto word
我们可以导航到自动词
instance of the service and when i click
服务实例，当我单击
here i get actually transferred to the
在这里，我实际上转移到了
defining beam definition which is the
定义光束定义是
inherited interface back to our
继承接口回到我们
configuration the next thing with regard
配置下一件事情
to admin support is supporting it in
管理员支持正在支持
method parameters so we have here a
方法参数，所以我们这里有一个
little demonstration purposes only a
很少的示范目的
wrapping of the original order service
包装原始订单服务
which we pass in in the order service
我们在订单服务中传递的
parameter of this method and we return
此方法的参数，我们返回
this instance here in another instance
这个实例在另一个实例中
of the beam as you can see we expect the
如您所见，我们期望
original instance of the odd or service
奇数或服务的原始实例
to be provided and again I can click
提供，然后我可以单击
here on the gutter icon and see that
在装订线图标上看到
it's correctly we solved in IntelliJ and
我们在IntelliJ中解决了
we can verify that our code is correct
我们可以验证我们的代码是正确的
here all right of course we can also
这里当然可以，我们也可以
override the default in we inherited
覆盖我们继承的默认值
from auto service config interface so
从自动服务配置界面
let's just do that and overwrite the
让我们这样做并覆盖
beam definition and maybe we want to
光束定义，也许我们想
provide a customer service which
提供客户服务
basically is just a fake implementation
基本上只是一个假的实现
of the existing order service just for
现有订单服务中仅用于
demonstration purposes and yeah we can
示范目的，是的，我们可以
see that Venus now set up correctly here
看到金星现在在这里正确设置
as well okay on to the next topic which
以及接下来的主题
is the support for allies for allies for
是对盟友的支持
is a new annotation from the spring
是春天的新注解
framework which allows you to redefine
允许您重新定义的框架
existing annotation parameters from the
来自的现有注释参数
built-in spring annotations
内置的弹簧注释
so what did I do here we define our own
所以我在这里做了什么，我们定义了自己的
annotation called my scanner it inherits
继承的注释称为我的扫描仪
from the components can annotation from
从组件可以注释
the spring framework we must make sure
春天的框架，我们必须确保
to add d at retention annotation to our
在保留注释中添加d
own element otherwise it won't be stored
自己的元素，否则将不会被存储
in the class and it cannot be used at
在课堂上，它不能用于
runtime from by the spring framework and
通过spring框架和
here we make use of realize for
在这里，我们利用实现
inpatient so basically what we can do is
住院，所以基本上我们可以做的是
to redefine existing attributes from the
从中重新定义现有属性
inheriting annotation in this case the
在这种情况下继承注释
components gain class and we can rename
组件获得类，我们可以重命名
for example the base packages attribute
例如基本包属性
here i renamed it to scan and of course
在这里，我将其重命名为扫描，当然
IntelliJ provides all the completion
IntelliJ提供所有完成
here as well filtered by the
这里也被
corresponding types from the parent
来自父级的相应类型
annotation and of course you can control
注释，您当然可以控制
click here and go to the original
单击此处并转到原始内容
definition are from the inherited a
定义是从继承的
notation as well so that's a nice way to
表示法，所以这是一种不错的方法
create your own custom made notations in
在中创建自己的自定义符号
everything from the default spring
一切都从默认的春天开始
annotations you can redefine attributes
您可以重新定义属性的注释
you can add your own attributes which is
您可以添加自己的属性
especially interesting for
对于特别有趣
alright test okay we are sorry we are
好吧测试好吧，我们很抱歉
streaming live from a conference and we
从会议现场直播
have some Wi-Fi problems it seems so
似乎有一些Wi-Fi问题
let's hope it stays stable ok back to
让我们希望它保持稳定还可以
the Allies for annotation this is
注释的盟友是
especially useful for your own
对您自己特别有用
annotations when you writing integration
编写集成时的注释
tests and you need to define some
测试，您需要定义一些
special attributes for your integration
集成的特殊属性
tests this is supported in IntelliJ 15
测试IntelliJ 15是否支持
now so let's take a look at our custom
现在，让我们来看看我们的习惯
testing annotation which is basically a
测试注释基本上是
meta annotation of the default at
默认位置的元注释
context configuration annotation
上下文配置注释
provided by the spring testing framework
由春季测试框架提供
again I'm overriding here one of the
再次，我在这里重载
existing attributes in this case the
在这种情况下，现有属性
classes every good and I just really
对每个商品进行分类，我真的
find it with my own name and i can add
用我自己的名字找到它，我可以添加
my own attributes or whatever i think is
我自己的属性或我认为是什么
necessary for my tests of course this is
我测试的必要条件当然是
also supported in the actual test model
实际测试模型中也支持
so here i have a small unit tests to run
所以在这里我要运行一个小单元测试
my order service test and the dependency
我的订单服务测试和依赖项
resolution and DB nikons are of course
分辨率和DB尼康当然是
as well properly detected here in my
以及在我这里正确检测到的
test model alright that's all about the
测试模型就好了
metal annotations and t at allies for
金属注释和盟友的
annotation support in IntelliJ 15 so the
IntelliJ 15中的注释支持，因此
next big topic is a key support for
下一个大话题是对
application events which is a very nice
应用程序事件，这是非常好的
way to send and receive events or
发送和接收事件的方式或
basically messages within your spring
基本上是你春天里的信息
application and let's take a look at
应用程序，让我们看一下
that so we have
这样我们有
this order service which basically takes
该订单服务基本上需要
an order ID and order status of
订单ID和订单状态
confirmed or unconfirmed and creates an
确认或未确认，并创建一个
order event beam which is then published
订购事件光束，然后发布
y r-d publisher instance field which is
第y个发布者实例字段，它是
an application event publisher which is
应用程序事件发布者
provided by spring this order event can
春季提供的此订单事件可以
just be an ordinary pocho bean or we can
只是一个普通的cho豆，否则我们可以
also inherit from the base class for
也从基类继承
education events and at our own
教育活动以及我们自己
attributes we have this source attribute
属性，我们有这个源属性
here which is basically defining the
这里基本上定义了
origin of the event so all we do here is
事件的起源，所以我们在这里要做的就是
just store those attributes here and now
只是在这里和现在存储这些属性
let's take a look at this nice little
让我们来看看这个漂亮的小东西
icon here next to the published event
已发布活动旁边的图标
invocation this is the new support for
调用，这是对的新支持
application events here in IntelliJ so I
IntelliJ中的应用程序事件在这里，所以我
can now navigate to the corresponding
现在可以导航到相应的
event listeners and apparently there are
事件监听器，显然有
a few so let's take a look at the
一些，让我们来看看
easiest one which is this one here any
最简单的一个，这是这里的任何一个
event listener just needs to be
事件监听器只需要
annotated with the event listener
用事件监听器注释
annotation and you can pass in a
注释，您可以传递
parameter of the expected event type so
预期事件类型的参数，因此
when we run this application we will
当我们运行此应用程序时，我们将
actually send in our event and we will
实际上发送我们的事件，我们将
just print out the order ID year and we
只需打印出订单ID年，我们
also support navigating back to the
还支持导航回
origins and also i can again click here
起源，我也可以再次点击这里
on you gotta icon and get back to any
在您必须的图标上，并返回到任何
event sender let's take a look at the
事件发送者让我们看一下
other implementations we have here as
我们在这里的其他实现
listeners so let's go to the or event
听众，让我们转到or事件
processor which is a bit more
处理器多一点
sophisticated again we have the event
再次复杂，我们有活动
listener annotation but here we find a
侦听器注释，但在这里我们找到一个
new attribute called condition
称为条件的新属性
so condition is basically just a springy
所以条件基本上是弹性的
el expression which you can add to your
您可以添加到您的el表达
method definition and it allows you to
方法定义，它使您能够
filter events which will actually be
过滤实际上将是
passed on to this method here we have
传递给这个方法，我们有
Auto completion here for the parameter
参数自动完成
for all the available beans for example
例如，对于所有可用的豆
and as you can see here the order then
就像你在这里看到的顺序
we pass in is also in the auto
我们通过也是在自动
completion list and of course since we
完成列表，当然，因为我们
know this type of the parameter we also
知道这种类型的参数
get all the completion for all the
得到所有的全部完成
attributes of this event again we can
我们可以再次将此事件的属性
invoke quick documentation we can also
调用快速文档，我们也可以
navigate there and all the usual
导航到那里和所有通常的
features of IntelliJ work in this
IntelliJ的功能在此工作
context as well so those two methods
上下文以及这两种方法
actually process different orders we
实际处理不同的订单
have one event listener processing all
有一个事件监听器处理所有
confirmed order orders and then we have
确认订单订单，然后我们有
one event listener processing only
一个事件监听器仅处理
special orders and special orders are
特别订单和特别订单是
just defined by this little spring AEL
刚刚由这个春天AEL定义
expression which checks the or ID for
用于检查或ID的表达式
the metric 42 ID so let's just quickly
公制42 ID，让我们快速
run our main class which is basically
运行我们的主要课程，基本上
just a minimal setup to instantiate the
只需最小的设置即可实例化
order service and our application
订购服务和我们的应用
context and here we will publish one of
上下文，在这里我们将发布以下内容之一
those events or events and when i run
这些事件或事件以及我何时跑步
this or event listeners with a trigger
带有触发器的this或event侦听器
and we see nothing because it's a dame
我们什么也看不到，因为那是一个女人
ok usually we should get the system out
好的，通常我们应该把系统拿出来
it worked before ok so much about the
它在确定之前就可以正常工作了
application events support and now let's
应用程序事件支持，现在让我们
go to the spring model dependency scrub
转到弹簧模型依赖项清理
let's switch to a different project here
让我们在这里切换到另一个项目
so what does the spring model dependency
那么弹簧模型的依赖性是什么
square you probably already know the
广场，你可能已经知道
existing graph for
现有图
spring beans where you can see all the
春豆在那里你可以看到所有
beans all the relationships between
豆之间的所有关系
beans for example all the wired
豆，例如所有有线
relationships or components kind
关系或组件类型
relationships and in IntelliJ 15 we
关系，在IntelliJ 15中
introduced a new diagram type which will
引入了新的图表类型
not show the beans but the underlying
不显示豆子，但底层
configuration files and their
配置文件及其
relationships so and usually in bigger
这样的关系通常更大
spring applications you will have not
春季应用程序，您将没有
only one screen configuration file or
仅一个屏幕配置文件或
class but many many of them and usually
课，但很多很多，通常
they will have quite a few relationships
他们将有很多关系
between them sometimes they are not very
他们之间有时他们不是很
easy to understand using at import for
易于理解在导入时用于
example or using some kind of star
例子或使用某种星星
import to match a certain set of files
导入以匹配特定的文件集
for example or using components can to
例如或使用组件可以
reach into other configurations on the
进入其他配置
class bus and that's something which is
类巴士，那是
really hard to understand especially if
真的很难理解，特别是如果
you are entering a new project or maybe
您正在输入一个新项目，或者
if you want to refactor an existing
如果您想重构现有的
spring configuration and you need to
弹簧配置，您需要
understand why some things are not
了解为什么有些东西不
working as you expect them to work so
像您期望的那样工作
this project is just a very artificial
这个项目只是一个非常人为的
project containing a huge list of Java
包含大量Java的项目
configuration classes here just normal
这里的配置类很正常
configuration classes without any beans
没有任何bean的配置类
and a huge list of XML configuration
以及大量的XML配置清单
files which in turn contain other
反过来包含其他文件
configuration setup select component
配置设置选择组件
scans and imports so when I invoke this
扫描并导入，所以当我调用此
spring water dependency square of now on
现在的泉水依赖广场
the diagrams menu I will actually see
我将实际看到的图表菜单
the resulting graph of all the
所有的结果图
configuration files so on the very left
配置文件在最左边
side we have our module then we have our
一边我们有我们的模块，然后我们有我们的
spring five sets which are defined in
弹簧五套
the spring facet and then we have those
春天的面，然后我们有那些
main notes basically which are refined
主要音符基本精制
in the spring file such so let's just
在春季文件中，所以让我们
quickly put this
快把这个
side so that's basically the top level
面，所以基本上是顶层
group of configuration files but as you
配置文件组，但与您一样
can see and when we move further to
可以看到，当我们进一步移动到
right there are many many more
对了还有很多
configuration files which we do not see
我们看不到的配置文件
in these infested configuration and
在这些出没的配置中
those are exactly the files which are
这些正是这些文件
imported or component scanned or
导入或扫描组件或
whatever other mechanism we support for
我们支持的其他任何机制
detecting and we see those edges we here
检测，我们在这里看到那些边缘
which are color-coded and telling us for
它们用颜色编码并告诉我们
example here we have a component scan on
在这里的示例中，我们有一个组件扫描
this note from XML to the config eClass
此说明从XML到config eClass
and so it's very easy to understand
所以很容易理解
where this configuration classes
该配置类在哪里
actually coming from and of course you
实际上来自你，当然你
can navigate to any of those nodes here
可以导航到这里的任何节点
and see what they're actually doing and
看看他们在做什么
we can also go to any of those nodes and
我们也可以去那些节点中的任何一个
see the defining configuration element
参见定义配置元素
for in this case components game let me
在这种情况下，组件游戏让我
show you another example of this spring
告诉你这个春天的另一个例子
configuration graph going back to the
配置图回到
world of spring boot as you might know
您可能知道的 spring boot 世界
in spring boot there's a lot of you know
在 spring boot 里，有很多人知道
some would call it magic involved are in
有些人会称其为魔术
the auto configuration of springboard so
跳板的自动配置
what happens behind the scenes is that
幕后发生的是
springwood comes with a huge list of
斯普林伍德带有大量的
auto configuration classes for all the
所有的自动配置类
frameworks and technologies it supports
它支持的框架和技术
and dusk those auto configuration
和黄昏那些自动配置
classes are automatically processed by
类由
springwood and they work and on several
斯普林伍德，他们工作，并在几个
conditions for example presence or non
条件，例如存在或不存在
presence of certain classes in the class
班上某些班级的存在
pass your application being a web
通过您的应用程序成为网络
application or not and many many other
是否申请以及许多其他申请
things and then basically set up on some
事情，然后基本上设置一些
kind of default configuration which is
一种默认配置是
the key to productivity and springwood
生产力和跳板的关键
or one of the keys and actually it would
或其中一个键，实际上
be interesting to see you um what this
看到你很有趣
or the configuration looks like at
或配置看起来像
runtime and you can do this here so what
运行时，您可以在这里执行此操作
I have prepared here is a very
我这里准备的是一个非常
artificial spring boot project using the
人工弹簧靴项目使用
latest spring with 123 snapshot actually
实际具有123快照的最新春季
and on the spring starter wizard I just
然后在spring starter向导上
checked all the dependencies which are
检查所有依赖项
available so that's a very artificial
可用，所以这是一个非常人为的
project but just to get as many notes as
项目，但只是获得尽可能多的笔记
possible and when we take a look at the
可能，当我们看一下
spring model dependency scruff sorry Val
弹簧模型依赖关系sc惜瓦尔
note I must click here then it doesn't
注意，我必须单击此处，否则不会
look too interesting because right now
看起来太有趣了，因为现在
what we see here is just the setup we
我们在这里看到的只是我们的设置
have in our own projects so we only have
有我们自己的项目，所以我们只有
our main class and that aligns duty at
我们的主要阶级，这与
swing GUI application that the normal
Swing GUI应用程序正常
spring book application class annotation
春季图书应用类注解
it becomes more interesting when we
当我们变得更有趣时
enable showing nodes defined to
启用显示定义为的节点
configuration nodes defined in libraries
库中定义的配置节点
so this is actually the graph of all the
所以这实际上是所有
auto configuration classes which are
自动配置类是
detected by intelligent and also process
通过智能检测并进行处理
by the way so let's take a quick a look
顺便说一下，让我们快速看一下
and you can see there's there's a huge
你会发现那里有一个巨大的
list of auto country creation classes
自动创建国家/地区类别列表
triggered by the springboard application
由跳板应用触发
which in turn trigger another set of
进而触发另一组
other configurations or import other
其他配置或导入其他
configuration so that's that's all the
配置，仅此而已
magic that is happening and spring boot
发生的魔法和春季启动
behind the scenes which you usually
通常在幕后
don't see but that's a nice way to
没有看到，但这是一个不错的方法
visualize what is happening with all the
可视化所有发生的事情
auto configuration and also great way to
自动配置也是很好的方法
debug maybe if you don't want to rely on
如果您不想依赖，请进行调试
the information you can get on the comes
您可以从中获得的信息
over from spring boot itself if there's
从弹簧靴本身，如果有
some error in your other configuration
您其他配置中的某些错误
and things are not working as you expect
事情并没有按您期望的那样工作
them to be
他们是
we have a few pair plans with the spring
我们有一些春季计划
model dependencies club as well so we
以及模型依赖俱乐部
are thinking to use it as a possible
正在考虑尽可能使用它
entry point for spring model set up
弹簧模型设置的入口点
related refactorings actually because we
相关重构实际上是因为我们
now have all this information emoto's
现在拥有所有这些信息emoto的
configuration files are related to each
配置文件与每个
other and there are some some
其他，还有一些
interesting things so we hope to come up
有趣的事情，所以我们希望能出现
with in the future this brings me to my
与未来这带我到我的
last small bit I want to talk about
我想谈的最后一点
today and that's the plans we have for
今天，这就是我们的计划
spring support and the next version of
春季支持和下一个版本
IntelliJ 15 note 1 so to stay just at
IntelliJ 15 note 1保持不变
this topic for auto configuration as you
本主题为您自动配置
can see the graph is quite complex
可以看到图很复杂
already we do support all the
我们已经支持所有
configuration model so it spring boot
配置模型，使其启动
plug in support in IntelliJ does scan
IntelliJ中的插件支持不会扫描
the order configuration files and acts
订单配置文件和行为
on the conditioners which are defined on
在护发素上定义
those and it doesn't work on all of
这些并不能在所有
those yet but we try to achieve the
那些，但我们尝试实现
eighty to ninety percent case working
百分之八十到百分之九十的案例
for IntelliJ 15 dot one so that for most
对于IntelliJ 15点一
auto configurations for most projects
大多数项目的自动配置
you will get the actual in model as it
您将获得实际的模型
will be at runtime just as if spring
将在运行时就像spring
boot would process all those auto
开机会处理所有这些自动
configuration classes for you another
另一个配置类
area of improvement is e application
改进领域是电子应用
tamil edit or support and there are a
泰米尔语编辑或支持，并且有一个
few missing bits yandel which we want to
我们想要的一些缺失的部分yandel
fix up for 15 not won the last topic for
修复15个未赢得最后一个主题的
spring boot in this area is further
这个区域的弹簧靴更远
improvements to the run configuration
运行配置的改进
attacked integration with the spring
与春天的融合
boot 1 dot 3 dev tools which is a very
启动1点3开发工具，这是一个非常
nice way to provide a auto v load of
提供自动v负载的好方法
your application classes while
您的应用程序类别
developing you spin good application
开发良好的应用程序
going more general to the other spring
到另一个春天更普遍
um we plan to update the existing
嗯，我们计划更新现有的
support for spring data spring security
支持spring数据spring安全性
and spring integration bring them up to
春季整合使他们成长为
the latest GA releases of spring and
春季和春季的最新GA版本
find out the film is in bits and pieces
找出电影是零零碎碎的
which have been editor and of course
一直是编辑，当然
another big topic is a cloud integration
另一个大话题是云集成
or support for cloud technology and the
或支持云技术和
IDE so we will try to rework our
IDE，所以我们将尝试重新设计我们的产品
existing integration and also make a
现有的整合，
stronger connection between running
跑步之间的联系更紧密
spring boot and running spring boot
弹簧靴和运行弹簧靴
applications on the cloud and further
云上的应用程序以及其他
improvements in that area are definitely
在这方面的改进肯定是
planned and the last big topic for 15
计划中的最后一个15大主题
dot one is to improve the support for
第一点是提高对
spring MVC the web framework from spring
Spring MVC Spring的Web框架
to enable most of the possibilities you
使您拥有大多数可能性
have to configure spring MVC by
必须通过配置Spring MVC
annotation support so that's all from me
注释支持，这一切都由我承担
I hope there was some interesting stuff
我希望有一些有趣的东西
for you to see and now we will switch
供您查看，现在我们将切换
switch to questions if you have any I
如果您有我，请切换到问题
want to thank our presenters for joining
要感谢我们的主持人的加入
us a great presentation make sure to
我们出色的演讲一定要
also check our website and of course
还要检查我们的网站，当然
send us your feedback on to let us know
向我们发送您的反馈意见，让我们知道
how we did it today and any suggestions
我们今天的工作方式和任何建议
you have take care everyone thank you
你保重大家谢谢
have a good day
祝你有美好的一天